techglobex.net 2019-07-17

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

**Privacy Policy for http://www.techglobex.net**  
The privacy of our readers and visitors at TechGlobeX.net is much precious to us.

**Personal Information**  
This privacy policy statement brings out the privacy exercises of web pages and services offered by TechGlobeX.net. If you need further details or asking any questions regarding our privacy policy statement, please feel free to contact us at tech.globex@gmail.com. This privacy policy drafts what kind of personal data and info we assemble and collect when you visit TechGlobeX.net, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
Like most of the other websites, TechGlobeX.net also collect, make and use the data contained in log files. The details and information inside the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) addresses, your type of browser (such as Internet Explorer, Firefox and Chrome), your ISP (Internet Service Provider such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the date and time you visited our website, website referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, track user's movement around the website, and gather demographic information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
TechGlobeX.net does utilize cookies to store several data and information which also includes your personal data and preferences when you visit our website, we also record user-specific information when any user access or visit different web pages and it also includes customize web page content based on visitors web browser type or other technical information which visitor or users send us from their different web browsers.

We also use and offer third-party adverting programs on TechGlobeX.net to support our website. These third parties advertisement vendors may use technology such as JavaScript’s, Web Cookies and Web Beacons when they offer advertisement through our website. For instance, our advertising partners (such as Google through the Google AdSense program and Infolinks through the In-Text Advertising program) use their desired cookies to track advertising stats such information including your IP address, your ISP, your web browser and in some cases, whether you have flash plugins installed or not. This is typically used for geotargeting purposes for showing certain ads based on specific sites visited or searched. For instance, (showing computer related ads to someone who frequently searches computer hardware and software) or (showing Canadian real estate ads to someone in Canada).

**DoubleClick DART Cookies**  
TechGlobeX.net may also use DART cookies to enable ads serving through Google’s DoubleClick program. Like many other advertising programs, Google as a third party advertising partner also uses cookies to enable and offer ads on our website. The usage of DART cookies from Google authorized them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other several websites on the web and internet.

TechGlobeX.net website visitors and users can know more about DoubleClick DART cookies by visiting the Google's Ad and Content Network privacy policies & principles webpage via official URL - [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/) Web visitors and user’s information and data tracking through the DART cookie technology are subject to Google’s own privacy policy.

At TechGlobeX.net, Our advertising vendors may use some cookies and web beacons on our website. These advertising partners include:

Google Adsense  
Infolinks  
Amazon  
Disqus

**Third-party External Website Links**  
TechGlobeX.net may also contain external links for your use and reference. Hence, we are not liable for the privacy policies or web content of such other third party websites. Every visitor and user of TechGlobeX.net must keep this in mind that when they leave our website, they must read the privacy policy statements of each external website because privacy policies of these websites may be different from us.

**Disclaimer**

**Use of Website Material**  
Every single web contents, text material, logos, images, graphics, website design and all other web elements at TechGlobeX.net Web Site are protected by copyrights and under the exclusive ownership of TechGlobeX.net and it also safeguards under the applicable Digital Millennium Copyright Act (DMCA) and Creative Commons (CC) Laws and Licenses, Therefore, our material and data may not be modified, copied, republished, imitated, distributed, circulated or transmitted in whole or in part without the prior written permission from TechGlobeX.net.

If you found any copyright violation, please report to us via Email: **tech.globex@gmail.com**.

**Change of Privacy Policy Statement**  
The Privacy Policy Statement on this page can get updated or changed at any time without any prior notice, so keep checking back. If you have any questions and queries regarding the privacy policy of TechGlobeX.net then you may [Contact Us](mailto:tech.globex@gmail.com).

_Privacy Policy Last Updated: February 2nd, 2018_
